https://www.performanceaudio.com/privacy/

The store will not work correctly in the case when cookies are disabled.
On Sale
Save $49.98!
Ultimate Support TS-80B Speaker Stands Bundle
Save $93.93!
Aston Microphones Stealth Microphone Bundle
Save $87.01!
Sennheiser ew 100 G4-ME4 Wireless Lavalier Bundle
Save $48.01!
Electro-Voice RE20 Mic & Cloudlifter Bundle
View All Items On Sale!
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is extremely important to Performance Audio. So we've developed a Privacy Policy that covers how we collect, use, disclose, transfer, and store your information. Please take a moment to familiarize yourself with our privacy practices and let us know if you have any questions.
Protecting your privacy is important to us. We strive to keep your personal information confidential. We safeguard the security of the data you send us with physical, electronic, and managerial procedures. We urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. For the highest security, we suggest you use a combination of letters and numbers for your password, and make sure you use a secure browser. The Performance Audio Web Store uses industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption on all web pages where personal information is required. To make purchases from the Performance Audio Web Store, you must use an SSL-enabled browser such as Safari, Netscape Navigator, or Internet Explorer. This protects the confidentiality of your personal and credit card information while it is transmitted over the Internet.
Performance Audio employees will NEVER ask for your password.
Performance Audio collects and uses your personal information to give you superior customer service and to provide you with convenient access to our products and services.
Like many websites, the Performance Audio Web Store uses "cookie" technology. When you first connect to our Web Store, the cookie identifies your browser with a unique, random number. The cookies we use do not reveal any personal information about you. Cookies aid in online shopping and help us understand which parts of our websites are the most popular, where our visitors are going, and how long they spend there. We use cookies to study traffic patterns on our site so we can make the site even better.
The Performance Audio website may contain links to other sites. We do not share your personal information with those websites and are not responsible for their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy policies of those companies.
Newsletter Subscribers OnlyWe may use your personal information to keep you up to date on the latest product announcements, software updates, special offers, and other information we think you'd like to hear about. This may occasionally include information from other related companies about products and services. From time to time, we may also use your personal information to contact you to participate in a market research survey, so that we can gauge customer satisfaction and develop better service.
The Performance Audio customer privacy policy is subject to change at any time. We encourage you to review the privacy policy regularly for any changes.
Get a Quote for
Customer Name
Customer Email
Phone Number
Comment
Submit
